<metadata>
  <title><![CDATA[ Twinge's Balance & Bugfix Mod ]]></title>
  <threadUrl><![CDATA[ http://www.ftlgame.com/forum/viewtopic.php?f=11&t=26269 ]]></threadUrl>
  <author><![CDATA[ Twinge ]]></author>
  <version><![CDATA[ 2.6.1 ]]></version>
  <description>
<![CDATA[

Full change list: http://www.it-is-law.com/ftl-balance/index.php?title=Main_Page

* Fixed multiple game bugs.
* Weak weapons made relevantly cheaper or otherwise improved. Best weapons more expensive, Flak I & Halberd less common.
* Many events tweaked to make more options actually worth considering.
* Stealth C's Shield+ Drone now requires 1 power; Engi B starts with Level 3 Piloting and Heavy Ion is buffed; Rock A starts with Explosive Replicator (with fewer missiles) and Hull Missile is buffed; Fed C starts with Repair Burst; Stealth B starts with Titanium System Casing.
* Kestrel C has been remade in an effort to make it a unique experience compared to other ships.
* Most augments improved or made cheaper. Adv. FTL Navigation removed from game. Long-Ranged Scanners & Reloaders cost more.
* Shield Drones now require 2 power and cost less. Fire Drone slightly weaker but only requires 2 power. Beam II and Anti-Combat Drones have been buffed slightly. Defense II and Combat II cheaper.
* System Pricing: Hacking much more expensive, Cloaking more expensive, Teleporters slightly cheaper. Many systems cheaper at the highest levels (including Engines). Cheaper to switch Medbay and Clone Bay.
* The Rebel Flagship now only has Level 2 Mind Control and Hacking when playing on Easy difficulty.
* Reduced the odds of free crew from events slightly and tweaked many event scrap gains up or down appropriately.
* Engi are slightly less common, and you get less free stuff in Engi Sectors.
* Various quality of life tweaks: easier beam aiming, more consistent event option ordering, better default weapon/crew positions, more informative text, etc.
* Large number of punctuation and grammar fixes. Event phrasing tweaked to be more consistent and clear.
* Fixed visuals on all ships, including shield positioning/size, cloaking lines, and system graphics.

If you want to help the development of content like this mod, consider watching my stream on Twitch: http://www.twitch.tv/darktwinge or supporting me on Patreon: http://www.patreon.com/DarkTwinge

]]>
  </description>
</metadata>